★个人制作:LnexplicableIZY.★  ★ 电影交流群 499155500★
塞尔维亚 贝克格拉德
是我的箱子吗？
Is that my case?
是的
It is.
那个是你的
That one is yours.
别掉以轻心
It's not to be taken lightly.
事实上 我有点希望他会自己现身
In fact, I was kind of hoping he would show up himself.
沃伊特先生就是这样
That's the thing about Mr. Voight.
他从不自己办事 他让别人替他办
He never does anything he can get someone else to do for him.
伯克希尔，马萨丘塞特
过的很愉快？
Enjoying yourself?
是啊 这地方真棒
Yeah, this place is incredible.
你叫什么名字
What's your name?
乔伊
Joey.
乔瑟夫 朋友们都叫我乔伊
Joseph. My friends call me Joey.
那我也叫你乔伊好了
Then so will I.
我叫赛琳娜
I am Serena.
那么 呃
So, um...
你认识他？沃伊特？
You know this guy? Voight?
其实我在他手下工作
Working for him, actually.
不是吧
No shit.
不骗人
我确信他会想见你
I'm sure he would love to meet you.
走廊尽头有个地方
There's a place at the end of the hall.
双层门
Double doors.
十分钟内去那
Be there in ten.
有人吗？
Hello?
赛琳娜？
Serena?
很美 对吧？
Beautiful, isn't it?
沃伊特先生 我···
JOEY: Mr. Voight, I...
有位女士 我刚刚···
There was this woman, and I was just...
抱歉
I'm sorry.
不用道歉
Don't apologize.
你可以拿着它
You can hold it.
只要回答问题就好
Just answer the question.
哦 呃···
Oh, uh...
确实很美
Yeah. It's really nice.
它是什么？
What is it?
它是···
It's...
一道谜题
It's a puzzle.
独一无二 被世人以往至今
The only one of its kind. Forgotten until now.
快解完了
And it's almost finished.
继续
Keep going.
如果我解开了 会有奖励吗？
So if I solve it, do I get a prize?
我会有奖励
I do.
等一下 我好像懂了
Wait, I think I got it.
嘿
Hey!
嘿 有人吗！
Hey, anybody!
发生什么了？
What's happening?
我不能···
I can't...
你他妈的对我做了什么？
What the fuck did you do to me?
啊！
Argh!
好疼···
The pain...
啊！
Argh!
我是伟大利维坦的
VOIGHT: I am a penitent
忏悔者
of the great Leviathan.
救命！
Please!
赐我拥趸
Grant me this audience.
赐我恩典
Grant me this boon.
用力 再用力
Harder. Go harder.
-你确定？ - 对 用力点
-Are you sure? -Yeah, harder.
不不 等等 等等
No, no. Wait, wait, wait.
让我转身
Turn me around.
好
Okay.
-好 继续 对 -这里？就在这？
-Okay, go. Yeah. -Here? Right here?
继续 继续 继续
Go, go, go.
速度怎么样？可以吗？
How's this speed? Is it good?
-你喜欢吗？ -喜欢
-You like that? -Yeah.
我好爱
I love it.
我爱你
I love you.
什么？等等
What? Wait, wait.
什么
TREVOR: What?
-好吧 我不应该说那个 -对
-Okay, I shouldn't have said that. -Yeah.
-没事 -我想我一瞬间晃神了
-No, it's fine. -I guess I got caught up in the moment.
没关系 崔弗 我就是觉得或许···
No, it's fine, Trevor. I just think maybe...
老天爷···
Jesus Christ...
嗨
Hi.
你们在做饭？
You guys were making food?
对 诺拉做了塔帕斯
Yes. Nora made tapas.
哦
Oh.
所以 这位是···
So, is this...
就是他？
This is him?
呃 这位是崔弗
Um, this is Trevor.
你跟他们提过我？
You told them about me?
就聊过一点
Okay. Just a little bit.
-好吧 好吧 -嘿 你好吗？
-Right, right. -Okay, hey. How are you?
挺好的
Good.
这位是我哥哥马特 和他男朋友科林
This is my brother Matt, and this is his boyfriend Colin.
-嘿 -嘿
-Hey. -Hey.
诺拉 室友
Nora, the roommate.
请坐 还有很多地方
Sit. There's plenty.
呃 坐下啊
Ah. Sit.
但我得走了 还有好几幅画要送
Yeah, you know, I should go. I've got a lot of paintings to deliver.
今天基本上是我的工作日 所以···
It's basically a workday for me, so...
-没问题 -好的
-No problem. -MATT: Cool.
我拿下外套
I'll get my jackets.
很高兴见到你们
Great to meet you guys.
用餐愉快
Enjoy dinner.
再见
Bye.
你们听到我俩做爱了？
You guys just heard us fucking?
-是啊 -对
-Yes, yeah. -Yeah.
有话就说 马特
Just say it, Matt.
我不喜欢他
I don't like him.
你只是因为他长得漂了而受到威胁了
You're just intimidated because he's a pretty boy.
What kind of guy hooks up with someone from a 12-step program?、
谁会选择和戒酒互助会上遇见的人约会啊？
认真的？
Honestly?
不然呢？
What?
你在吐槽我俩吗？
Is that supposed to be a stab?
莱莉 不是这样的
Riley, it's not like that.
我在担心你
And my concern is you.
万一他再次酗酒 你会怎么办？
How you're going to handle it when he's relapsing.
你已经戒了好几个月 差不多半年了？
You've been sober for months. What, almost half a year?
对
Yeah.
别把我的癖好都剥夺
Don't take away all my vices.
我只是想上个可爱的男孩 老天爷
Let me fuck a cute guy, for Christ's sake.
你们把电视声音关小就是为听我们吵架吗？
Did you really just turn down the TV to listen to us argue?
-没有 -没有
-No. -No.
天呐 这里没人把我当回事
God, no one takes me seriously here.
那是因为你太关心所有人了
That's because you do it enough for everyone.
是啊 总有人得关系你们
Yeah, well, someone's got to.
月初很快要到了
The first of the month is coming up real fast.
我不能一直帮你交房租了
I can't keep covering you.
我知道 没人要你帮我
I know that. Nobody is asking you to.
最近小费很少
Tips have been shit lately.
-我在努力了 -好吧
-I'm trying. -Okay.
小莱 我爱你
Ri, I love you.
我想让你快乐 并不想监管你的每一个人生选择
I want you to have fun. I'm not out here trying to police your every life choice.
我只是想确保我能照顾好自己
You just want to make sure that I can handle myself.
对吗？
Right?
信息已接收 我不会再见他了
Message received. I won't see him.
是这样的
Here's the thing.
他没做错什么 这才是问题
He's not wrong. That's the problem.
他什么也没做错而且是出于好意
He's not wrong and he means well,
这让我特别想给他一拳
and that makes me want to fucking swing on him.
我会替你上
I'll swing on him for you.
随便吧
Whatever.
我不需要他为我骄傲或怎样
I don't need him to be proud of me or anything.
只要他不因我蒙羞就好
It'd just be a little nice if he wasn't ashamed.
随他吧
TREVOR: Just let it go.
-别聊这个了 -那我们干什么？
-We're not doing that. -What the fuck are we doing?
我们···
We are...
我们俩现在陪着对方
We're being lonely together.
怎么 你难道有更好的地方可去？
Why, you got somewhere better to be?
有 应该去找份工作了
Yeah. Should be looking for a job.
你有工作啊
You got a job.
我知道 我是说···
No, I know. I mean...
更好的工作
Better job.
受够破产的日子了
I'm really tired of being broke.
怎么了？
What?
你想说什么？
算了
Forget it.
你哥哥不会喜欢这个主意的 所以···
Your brother wouldn't like it, so...
好吧 他也不喜欢我来这里啊
Okay, well, he also would not like me being here.
只要他不知道就没影响了
Can't hurt him if he doesn't know.
好吧 你说得对
Okay, right. Yeah.
但这个主意 对你有点影响
But, see, it hurts you.
你可能不是个好女孩 莱莉 但你本质不坏
You might not be a good girl, Riley, but you want to be.
马特就像守护小天使一样时刻坐在你肩膀上警醒着你
You got a little Matt just kind of sitting on your shoulder.
所以他的意见你应该听一听
So, he may be worth listening to, you know.
大概吧
Maybe.
现在你可以跟我说了吧
Now you can tell me.
没什么好说的
There's nothing to tell.
崔弗 告诉我
Tell me, Trevor.
嘿 住手
Hey. Stop.
-冷静点 -告诉我
-Calm down. -Tell me.
-好了 好了 -快说
-All right, all right, all right. -Tell me.
呃
Uh...
好吧 你知道我经常跑仓库区送货吧？
Okay. So, you know how I always make runs down to the warehouse district?
-知道 -那里有个仓库
-Yeah. -So, there's this one spot
我们去送过货
that we used to drop stuff off at.
匿名的
Totally anonymous.
没有人见过里面有人
Nobody's ever seen anyone in there,
但搬进搬出的那些东西
but, like, the shit they had coming in and out,
看起来超级值钱
it's like billionaire shit.
我路过好几次 我发誓那间仓库是废弃的
So I pass it sometimes and I swear it's abandoned.
基本全是废弃的 除了最后那一箱货
Totally abandoned except for one last shipment.
你是想破门而入吗？
So you want to break in?
没必要 我记得门锁密码
Don't have to. I remember the key code.
那箱货是什么东西？
What's in the shipment?
不知道
Don't know.
是谁的东西呢？
Who does it belong to?
我不知道啊 可能属于某个想要大赚一笔的有钱混蛋吧
I don't know. I mean, some rich asshole who's looking to make a profit.
他们不会注意到有东西不见了
They're not going to miss it.
给我搭把手 我就算你一份
Give me a hand, I'll cut you in.
你知道吗？
You know what?
把我说得话忘了吧
Forget I said anything
因为你正在努力重新振作起来
because, you know, you're trying to get your shit together,
我可不想做你的绊脚石
and I don't wanna get in the way of that, so...
闭嘴吧 崔弗
Shut up, Trevor.
好了
All right.
开弓没有回头箭 你确定你想这么做吗？
Point of no return. You sure you want to do this?
是吗？
Yeah?
动手吧
Let's go.
好嘞
Okay.
让我们瞧一瞧
Let's see here.
好啊
Okay.
你怎么看？
What do you think?
你这是什么意思？
What do you mean?
你知道密码吗？
Do you know the combination?
呃 不知道···
Well, no. Um...
我不知道
I don't.
要是我都弄不开 你就更别想了
No chance you could get it if I couldn't.
凡事都讲究诀窍的
There's a trick to everything.
好吧 确实
Right, yeah.
试试看吧
Let's see it.
好啊
Okay.
来瞧瞧里面有什么
Let's see here.
-你能搞定吗？ -当然
-Can you get it? -Yeah.
你能弄开它吗？
Can you get it open?
老天爷啊 盒子套盒子
God damn. Boxes within boxes.
天啊
Jesus.
这玩意怎么开
How does it open?
就是这个吗？
Is that it?
该死
Fuck!
老天 我还以为里面会有一捆债券或者类似的东西
God, I thought there'd be like a stack of bonds or some shit.
这东西应该挺值钱的
It's got to be worth something.
好吧 但愿如此
Let's hope so. Yeah.
如果你不想要就给我吧
I'll take it if you don't want it.
好啊 可以
Yeah. Yeah.
要不你先拿着吧？
Why don't you hold on to it for now?
我在看看能不能找个鉴定师来
I'll see if I can find some kind of appraiser,
看能卖多少钱 我们俩再一起分 行吗？
and we'll split whatever cash we can get from it, yeah?
好
Okay.
“波涛已去 浪潮止息”
"The waves were dead, the tides were in their grave"
“凝滞的气流里风也断绝”
"The winds were withered in the stagnant air"
“硝烟云逸”
"and the clouds perished"
“他们留存无益 因为黑暗”
"Darkness had no need of aid from them"
“便是宇宙自己”
"She was the Universe."
该死
Shit.
雪莱的
Shelley.
肯定是珀西·雪莱写的
Percy Shelley.
不是
No.
-玛丽·雪莱 -是拜伦
-Mary. -Byron.
该死啊
Fuck!
他妈的居然是拜伦
Fucking Lord Byron.
她没事的 让她自己待着吧
She's fine. Leave her alone.
嘿
Hey.
你别想下床
Do not fucking leave this bed.
好吧
Okay.
你吓到我了
You scared me.
我今晚没看到你 你去哪儿了？
I missed you tonight? Where'd you go?
出去了
Out.
喝酒了吗？
Drinking?
没喝
Mmm-mmm.
放屁 你连鞋子都脱不下来了
Bullshit. You can't even take off your shoes.
因为屋子里很黑
It's dark in here
我努力不想吵醒你来着
and I was trying not to wake you up.
别明知道我回答不上来还问好吧 马特
Don't ask me questions if you know I can't answer them, Matt.
嗑药了吗？
Pills?
没有
No.
-真没有··· -好吧 让我看看
-No, seriously... -Okay, Let me see.
天呐 马特 我真他妈的没嗑
Christ, Matt, I'm fucking clean.
-嘿 我就是担心你 小莱··· -滚出我房间
-Hey, I worry about you, Ri... -Get out of my room!
莱莉 我不是要···
Riley, I'm not trying...
我爱你
I love you.
你就是喜欢当救世主 哪怕你住再这破公寓
You love having something to fix, so that you can feel like
你也能获得巨大的满足感
a big success in this shitty apartment...
好了 我明白你想干嘛了
Okay, I see what you're trying to do.
不 你对我想做的事一无所知 我不是···
No, you don't know a thing about what I'm trying to do, I'm not...
你知道吗？ 这么关系
You know what? That's okay.
-我也不知道 -好吧
-Neither do I. -Okay.
你喝醉了
You're drunk.
是啊 你嫉妒吗？
Yeah! Are you jealous?
-你怕了吗？ -睡觉吧 醒醒酒
-Are you scared? -Sleep it off.
明天早上收好你的破烂滚蛋
And in the morning, pack your shit.
你不是认真的
You don't mean that.
不是个屁
The hell I don't.
那你就说啊
Then say it.
说得像那么回事啊
Like you mean it.
滚出去
Get the fuck out!
你滚出去
非得这么说是吗？你满意了？
Like that? You happy?
我总是不知道你会惹上什么麻烦
I don't know what's gonna happen to you, ever!
你要是想赌 你就会输的 莱莉
You want to play games, you will lose, Riley.
收拾好你的破烂 滚出我家
Pack your shit. Get the fuck out of my house.
还以为你永远不会说出口呢
I thought you'd never ask!
再见 科林
So long, Colin.
说真的 回屋里去吧
Seriously, come back inside.
今晚只是不太顺而已
It's just a bad night.
好吗 你一会儿会后悔的
Okay? You're just going to regret this later.
该死
Fuck!
你到底事什么呢？
So, what's your deal?
该死
Shit.
我把你弄坏了吗？
Did I break you?
该死的
Holy shit.
什么鬼？
What the fuck?
那刀片
That blade
本来是为你准备的
was meant for you.
谁在那？
Who's there?
跟我们走
Come with us.
如果不是你
If not you...
就给我们带另一个来
...bring us another.
不 不 不
No, no, no...
怎么了？你
What's up? Were you...
你做噩梦了吗？
Were you having a bad dream?
嗯
Yeah.
应该是
Yeah, I guess so.
给她打个电话吧
Just call her.
她不会接的
She won't answer.
等下 你要现在出去吗？
Wait, you're leaving now?
莱莉
Riley.
小莱
Ri.
嘿
Hey!
小莱 不 不 不要
Ri! No, no, no.
嘿
Hey.
嘿 醒醒 醒醒
Hey, come on. Come on.
你磕了什么药？
Hey, what did you take?
What did you take?
小莱？
Ri?
啊
Argh!
-莱莉 谢天谢地 -怎么了？
-Riley. Hey, thank God. -What?
我在这儿
I'm here.
你手受伤了
Your hand.
是
Yeah.
好 来 起身
Okay. Okay, come on.
我扶着你
I got you.
我们慢慢下去
Okay, we're going down.
好 好
Okay. Okay.
没事了 你还好吗？
All right. You good?
我去把血冲掉 你保持清醒 好吗？
I'm going to rinse this off and you're going to stay awake. Yeah?
保持清醒
Stay awake.
马特？ 怎么回事
Matt? What...
没事了 往上看
All right, look up.
你今晚服用了什么吗？
Did you take something tonight?
药丸？还是别的什么？
Pills? Anything?
我不记得了
I don't remember.
你把别的东西混进酒里一起喝了吗？
Did you mix anything with the alcohol?
我不记得了
I don't remember.
-有消息吗？ -没有
-Is there any luck? -No.
-有消息吗？ -也没有
-Any word? -No.
所以现在怎么办？
So what now?
我们接下来该做什么？
I mean, what should we do?
我们大概得等着 因为警察也没法做什么
I guess we wait 'cause the cops can't do anything yet.
他们说水槽上的几滴血不够立案的
They said a couple drops of blood on the sink isn't enough.
很显然 那可能不是他的血
Apparently, it might not even be his.
那是马特的血
It's Matt's blood.
你怎么知道的 莱莉？
How do you know that, Riley?
我告诉过你了 他被这个划伤了
I told you he cut himself on this.
那个？那是什么东西？
On that? What is that?
你没跟我们说过那个东西
You didn't tell us about that.
我不知道 我不知道
I don't know. I don't know.
我不···
I didn't...
我完全混乱了 好吗？
I was really fucked up, okay?
我在飘飘欲仙 没想到马特来找我了
And I was in and out of it, and I wasn't expecting for Matt to just be there.
而且药效上来了 我看见了一些东西
And the pills were kicking in, and I was seeing things.
-什么东西 -我不知道
-What things? -I don't know.
我不知道 很莫名其妙的
I don't know. It was just crazy fucked-up shit.
你们想让我告诉你们···
You wanted me to tell you...
对 跟我们说说马特
Yeah, tell me about Matt.
-他说了什么 做了什么 -我正在说
-What he said, what he did. -I am.
他把我叫醒 他的手流血了
He woke me up, his hand was bleeding.
他走进了洗手间 然后再也没有出来
He went into the bathroom and then he never came out.
等一下 你没看见他出来？
Wait, you never saw him come out?
但你刚刚说你在飘飘欲仙 完全他妈的嗨了
But you just said that you were in and out of it, fucking blitzed.
你错过了什么？
So what did you miss?
因为他不会就那样离开的 他不是这样的人
Because he wouldn't just leave. That's not him.
我知道 我知道 我知道
I know, I know. I know that.
所以好好想想 莱莉 拜托了
So fucking think, Riley. Please.
我···
I...
我在努力了
I'm trying.
我告诉过你不要离开
I told you not to leave.
-莱莉 -不 我只是···
-Riley. -No, I just...
莱莉
Riley.
嘿 你来干什么？
Hey. What are you doing here?
吻我
Kiss me.
发生什么了？
What happened?
什么？
What?
-什么 -那边那个···
-What? -There's a...
到底是他妈怎么回事？
What the fuck is happening?
什么 什么 你在说什么？莱莉
What, what, what? Riley.
什么东西？你看见什么了？
What is it? What is it?
我不知道
I don't know.
好吧 呃···
Okay, um...
你吃了几粒？
How many did you take?
3粒
Three.
-跟之前一样的药？ -对 一样的药
-Same stuff? -Yeah, it's the same shit.
我之前从来没产生过这么强烈的幻觉
It's never made me full-on hallucinate before.
而且我现在药效已经过了
I'm not on anything right now.
为什么我还他妈能看见那个鬼东西？
Why the fuck am I seeing shit still?
我知道 我知道
I know, I know.
所以我们现在摊开来说 好吗？
That's why we're laying all this out, okay?
你怎么让它变化的
How did you get it to change,
从一个立方体变成这样？
like, from the cube into that?
我没动它
I didn't.
它自己变成那样的
It changed on its own.
看
Look.
这是个谜题
It's a puzzle.
你看 这些组件可以活动
See? The pieces move.
如果你能把它卡在正确的位置上 就解决了这个谜题的一部分
If you get 'em to lock into place, then you solve a part of it.
但现在 他就像···
But now, it's like...
它···
It's...
像是到了下一个阶段什么的
It's on the next step or something.
-来 你试试 -我才不要
-Here. You try. -Fuck no.
你不相信我吗？
You believe me?
我当然相信你 但我也说了 我不玩这种傻逼玩意
Yeah, of course. I told you, I don't fuck with shit like that.
但你真的相信我吗？
Yeah, but you really believe me?
这是什么东西？它是从哪儿来的？
What is this thing? Where did it come from?
我不知道
I have no idea.
那些集装箱呢？
So, what about the shipping container?
那是谁的集装箱？
Whose shipping container is that?
我不知道 好吗？
I don't know, okay?
没有人来认领
They never showed up to claim it, so...
那栋建筑呢？谁是那栋楼的主任？
And the building? Who owns the building?
我们能查出来吗？这肯定跟某个人有关联
Well, can we find out? There has to be a name somewhere.
莱莉 我感觉我们有点疯狂了
Riley, this feels a little crazy.
只有这一个赛琳娜·曼纳可
There are no other Serena Manakers.
我只是想和她聊聊
I just want to talk to her.
你有访客
You have visitors.
赛琳娜？
Serena?
嗨
Hi.
我知道你不认识我们
I know you don't know us.
我是莱莉·麦肯德瑞
My name's Riley McKendry,
这是我的朋友崔弗
and this is my friend Trevor.
我们有一些问题想要咨询您
And we actually have a few questions that we wanted to ask you,
如果您愿意的话
if that's okay.
可能我们来得不是时候
Maybe it's a bad time.
不是时候？
Bad time?
我的肺正在腐烂
My lungs are rotting out.
我他妈要死在这里了
I'm fucking dying in this place.
你们想问什么？
What's this about?
一间仓库
A warehouse.
你得说的更具体一点
You'd have to be more specific.
仓库的合约上有你的名字
Your name was on the deed.
你运进去了一些东西
You had something shipped in.
至今还在里面
It's still there.
不是运进去的
It wasn't shipped in.
是被锁在那里
It was locked up.
而且也不是我的东西
And it isn't mine.
那你能告诉我那是谁的东西吗？
Well, can you tell us whose it is?
你们怎么知道那个东西的？
How do you know about this?
你们为什么关心这个问题？
And why do you care?
你们完全不知道自己卷入了什么事
You have no idea whose business you've stepped in.
罗兰·沃伊特是个邪恶的虐待狂
Roland Voight was monstrous and sadistic.
罗兰·沃伊特？
Roland Voight?
是你上司的名字吗？
Is that who you work for?
我帮他处理了一次房产纠纷
I sorted out his mess of an estate.
那是我为他做的最后一件事
And that was the last thing I ever did for him.
我不为自己做的事而骄傲
Not proud of the things I did.
你在查的这个东西很危险
What you're after is dangerous.
它终结了沃伊特的生命
It ended Voight's life,
它也会终结你的
and it will end yours, too.
-甚至更糟 -去他妈的
-Or worse. -Fuck this.
妈的 莱莉
Fuck, Riley.
我们走
Let's go. Come on.
莱莉
Riley.
莱莉？
Riley?
我们走啊
Let's go.
这是你刚说的那东西吗？
Is this what you're talking about?
谁把这个打开了？
Who opened this?
这不是它的初始形态
This is not the first configuration.
谁碰它了？
Who touched it?
我哥哥
My brother.
他现在不在了 对吧？
And now he's gone, isn't he?
所以 你现在见过他们了
So you've seen them.
罗兰曾经也能见到他们
Roland used to see them, too.
别人都以为他疯了
People thought he was crazy.
罗兰称他们为天使
Angels, he called them.
谁曾想 恶魔居然识不出恶魔
You'd think a devil would know a devil.
我们走吧
Let's go.
给我拿点水
Get me some water.
-崔弗 去拿水 -好 知道了
-Trevor, go get it. -Okay, I got it.
我要把这个拿走 这是为了你好
I'm taking this back for your own good.
嘿 把它放下
Hey, why don't you put that down?
我要把它锁起来
I'm locking it up.
对不起 别的我也无能为力了
I'm sorry, I've got nothing else for you.
什么？别这样 还给我
What? Come on, give it to me.
-把它给我 赛琳娜 -不
-Give it to me, Serena. -No.
-赛琳娜 -不行
-Serena! -No!
赛琳娜 快还给我
Serena, please give it back.
你不知道你面对的是什么
You don't know what you're doing.
还给我
Give it back!
啊
Argh!
好疼
Ow!
怎么了？
What happened?
-怎么了？ -没事
-What happened? -It's okay.
是我的错
I did it to myself.
-刚刚他妈的发生什么了？ -我不知道
-What the fuck happened in there? -I don't know.
她···
She...
那玩意就放在卓上 然后她拿起来了···
The thing was on the table, then she picked it up...
那说明我们就不该来这里 不是吗？
That proves coming here was a bad idea, then, right?
你在胡说什么？她刚刚还说我哥不在了
What are you talking about? She said that he's gone.
她怎么会知道？她怎么可能知道？
How would she know that? How would she know that?
慢点说 慢点说
Slow down, slow down.
冷静一点 我们来捋一捋这些 好吗？
Slow down. Let's just unpack everything, all right?
有太多要消化了
This is a lot to process here.
崔弗 我们又他妈不是在开会
We're not in a fucking meeting, Trevor.
真抱歉我他妈还想着要帮你
Sorry for trying to fucking help.
她现在头很晕
She's feeling faint.
她把自己割伤了 很严重
She cut herself pretty bad.
医生刚刚出去了
The doctor just stepped out.
-我去看看 说不定医生还在 -好的
-Let me check. Maybe she's still here. -Okay.
她正在上早班
She's in the day shift.
有人吗？
Hello?
对不起
I'm sorry.
我为我做过的那些事道歉
I'm sorry for what I have done.
求你手下留情
Have mercy.
省点力气
Save your breath
留着尖叫吧
for screaming.
-崔弗··· -我回来了
-Trevor... -Hey.
快来
Hi. Come here.
我刚发现这个叫沃伊特的很诡异
I just found so much weird shit about this Voight guy.
各种乱七八糟的性侵事件 还有洗钱的指控
All sorts of fucked-up sex stuff. Accusations of money laundering, too.
然后六年前 他突然消失了
And then six years ago, he just disappears.
没人知道发···
Nobody knows what...
怎么了？
What? What's wrong?
那个律师也不在了
Um, the lawyer's gone, too.
什么？
What?
-你说什么？ -曼纳可
-What are you talking about? -Manaker.
我刚刚很担心她 就打了电话过去
I called because I was worried about her hand
他们说她不在那了
and they said that she wasn't there.
她之前还在医务室里 但刚刚又不在了
She was in the infirmary, and then she wasn't,
也没人看见她离开 所以···
and no one saw her leave, so...
-我操 -是啊 操他妈的
-Fuck. -Yeah. Fuck!
莱莉 我们得扔了这玩意
We need to get rid of that thing, Riley.
知道吗？
All right?
你干什么？
What are you doing?
先是我哥 然后是赛琳娜·曼纳可
First my brother, then Serena Manaker.
跟六年前一模一样
The same exact shit six years ago.
就发生在沃伊特消失前的那几周
In the weeks leading up to Voight's disappearance,
还有其他消失的人
there were others, too.
有个勤杂工 一个性工作者
There was a grooundkeeper, a sex worker,
甚至可能有其他大家都不知道的人
and there were probably ones that nobody even knew about,
他们多少都和沃伊特还有他的庄园
and they're all loosely connected to him
有关联 而且他们都他妈的消失了
and his estate, and they're all fucking gone.
他们全都消失了
They're all gone.
这事再次发生了 这个沃伊特
It's happening again. I know that this guy
脱不了干系 这个装置也是
has something to do with it, and I know that that thing does, too.
他会打开 然后把人割伤
It opens up and it cuts you.
有人一旦被割伤 就···
And then when it does, you...
我们必须去那里
We have to go there.
去他的庄园 并不远
To his estate. It's not that far.
要接吗？
Gonna get that?
接
Yeah.
嘿 科林 怎么样？
Hey, Colin. What's up?
嘿 你怎样了？你在哪？
Hey, what's up? Where are you?
我现在暂时待在崔弗家
I'm hanging out at Trevor's for now.
好 他家在哪？我来接你
Okay. Where is his place? I'll come get you.
没事 不用来 我正有事
No, that's okay. I'm doing stuff.
我们都有事
We're all doing stuff.
好吗？
Okay?
但我们应该一起处理这件事
But we should be doing this shit together
因为我他妈的不知道还能做什么了
'cause I don't know what the hell to do here.
这是这整件事最糟糕的部分
That's the fucked-up part of all this shit.
如果马特在 他也会这么说
Like, Matt would.
是啊 他会这么说
Yeah, he would.
所以 我要去接你
Okay, so, I'll come and get you.
莱莉？
Riley?
崔弗
Trevor!
崔弗 你他妈的在···崔弗
Trevor, what the fuck are you... Trevor!
我要把这玩意扔了 没人能察觉到差别
I'm tossing this thing. No one'll know the difference.
差就差在 我需要用它来找到马特
The difference is, I need it to find Matt.
Don't you get that?你难道不懂吗？
我们至少商量一下吧 行不行？
Can we at least talk about it? Please.
商量一下？
Talk about it?
你之前都不想聊这件事 所以你他妈才把它拿走了
You didn't wanna talk about it . That's why you took it!
我以为你相信我
I thought you believed me.
我相信 我相信
I do. I do!
莱莉 我相信你 行不行？
I do believe you, Riley, all right?
我还以为我能信任你
And I thought that I could trust you!
有人吗？
Hello?
莱莉···
Riley...
马特？
Matt?
莱莉···
Riley...
马特
Matt!
-救我 -你在哪？
-Help me. -Where are you?
莱莉
Riley!
马特
Matt!
真的是你吗？
Is it really you?
你希望是我吗？
Do you want it to be?
我的天
Oh, my God.
我的天啊
对不起
I'm so sorry.
真的对不起
带我回去吧
Bring me back.
莱莉 莱莉 是我 科林
Riley, Riley. It's me, it's Colin.
是我
It's me.
怎么回事
I don't understand.
没事了 亲爱的 我们都在
It's okay, sweetie. We're here.
现在他妈的什么情况？
What the fuck is going on?
我们跟崔弗聊过了 然后在这找到了你
We talked to Trevor and came to find you.
门开着而且我们听到你的尖叫
The door was open. We heard you screaming.
你需要帮忙吗？
Figured you'd need some help.
帮助？
Help?
不不不 我不需要
I don't need help.
-帮什么？ -我们来这儿带你回家
-With what? -We're just here to bring you home.
不 我不回家
No, I'm not going home.
我在这里是有原因的
I'm here for a reason.
我不会回去的
I'm not going home.
-能让我们单独待一会儿吗？ -真的吗？
-Could you give us a second? -Seriously?
-莱莉 我们要···什么？ -嘿 别管了
-Riley, we need to... What? -Hey, leave it.
相信我吧
Just trust me on this, dude.
我们就在楼上等着 很高兴你没事
We'll be upstairs. I'm so glad you're okay.
-莱莉 -没关系的 就一会儿
-Riley. -It's okay, give them a second.
有人住在这里吗？
Does someone even live in this place?
我的意思是 这是什么？
I mean, what is this?
我们在干什么？
All right, what are we even doing here?
我们不就应该拉上莱莉赶快跑吗？
Okay, let's just grab Riley and just get the hell out, right?
冷静点
Hey, chill.
又不是第一次到处找她了
Isn't the first time we've had to track her down.
给她点空间吧
Just give her some space.
空间？好吧
Space? Yeah.
好吧好吧
All right.
来看看这鬼地方有什么东西
Might as well see what they got left.
嗯···
Um...
好吧···
Okay...
瞧瞧
Bingo.
好吧
All right.
要来一杯吗 女士？
What's your pleasure, ma'am?
莱莉还在这儿呢 别喝了
We don't drink when Riley's around.
好吧 好吧
Right, right.
嗯···
Um...
我去下厕所 去去就回
Okay. I'm gonna find a bathroom real quick.
好
Sure.
这到底是什么地方？
What is this place?
我也不知道
I don't know.
可能是个SM地牢吧？
A fuck dungeon?
你不想告诉我这都是怎么回事吗？
Do you want to tell me what this is about?
操 对不起
Fuck! Sorry.
对不起 对不起
Sorry. Sorry.
老天爷
God.
据沃伊特的笔记上说 这个盒子
So, according to Voight, the puzzle box
一共有六面 六种形态 现在还剩下三种
it has six sides and six configurations. There are three left.
书上说只要持有了最后一种形态“利维坦之盒”
Then it says whoever possesses the final configuration,
就可以打开去另一个世界的通道
is granted a passage to another realm
换句话说就是可以“见到神明”
to an "audience with God."
莱莉 你什么时候开始相信这些鬼神之事的？
Riley, since when do you believe in God?
我的意思是 这位神明
What I'm trying to get to is that this God, whatever it is,
将会为持有“利维坦之盒”的人提供选择
offers choices to whoever holds the final configuration.
可以满足你的欲望
Get there, then you choose your ultimate desire.
生命 知识 爱情
Life, knowledge, love,
感觉 力量 复生
sensation, power, resurrection.
你知道我想得到什么吗？
You see where I'm going?
不 我不知道
No, I don't, actually.
马特
Matt.
要是这可以把他带回来呢？
What if this brings him back?
好吧 莱莉
Okay. Riley.
收拾收拾咱们该出去了
Let's just close this up and get outta here.
不 不
No, no.
我知道这听起来很荒谬
I know that it sounds crazy,
-但是我真的很想让他回来 -这一切太复杂了 莱莉
-but I want to bring him back. -This is a lot, Riley.
科林？
Colin?
操
Shit!
该死
Fuck!
崔弗
Trevor.
Trevor!
-诺拉 -老天 你吓到我了
-Nora. -Jesus Christ. You scared me.
你没事关门干什么？
Why did you shut the door?
我没有啊 你喊我的名字我就回来了
I didn't. You called my name. I came back.
你怎么找到的
How the hell did you find...
快把我弄出去 吧台后面有个板子
Get me out of here. There's a panel behind the bar.
上面有一个按钮可以开门
One of the switches.
好的 好的 稍微等一会儿
Okay, okay. Hold tight. All right?
-好了 好了 莱莉 -但是
-Okay. Yes, yes, Riley. -But, I...
你说的够多了 我明白
It's just a lot. It's a lot, and I get it.
我已经听懂了
I get it. I get it.
好吧
Okay?
我不是质疑你
I'm not questioning you,
我只是不相信这上面的东西
I'm just questioning this.
我们必须先改变盒子的形态
The box. You have to get it to change.
我们需要先献祭
You have to mark a sacrifice.
他们就会过来收集
And then they come to collect.
就是这样
That's how you get your price.
这儿 看
Here, look.
等等 盒子 盒子不见了？
Wait where's the... Where is the box?
盒子不在我这儿了
I don't have it.
你找到了吗？
Have you found it?
还在找
Yeah.
那个按钮啊？
Which switch?
全都试一遍吧
Try all of them.
好吧 好吧
All right, all right.
TREVOR: Anything?
NORA: No.
你找到
Have you found...
诺拉
Nora!
不 不 不
No, no, no.
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
你还好吗？你还好吗？
Hey, are you okay? Are you okay?
-发生什么了？ 你的背？ -我的背
-What happened? Your back? -My back.
这是什么？这他妈是什么？
What the fuck is that? What the fuck is that?
我先把它给
Okay? I'm gonna...
别 别 别
No, no, no!
有一把刀啊
There's a knife in that.
该死 该死
Oh, fuck. Oh, shit.
快 快压住止血
I'm gonna try to apply pressure.
压住
Pressure.
发生什么事了？
What happened?
怎么回事？
不知道 我们刚刚在另外一间房间里
I don't know. We were in the other room.
帮我把他扶起来 快点
Help me get her up, then.
我的天啊 诺拉
Oh, my God. Nora.
有人在墙里
There was a man in the walls.
她说什么？
What did she say?
不知道 她快休克了
I don't know. She's out of it.
我们得快点走
We need to leave.
快叫救护车啊
We need to call an ambulance.
我们现在就得走
We need to leave. Now!
我们需要离开这里
We need to get out of here.
她有麻烦了
She's in danger.
把她架起来 快
Get her up off the floor. Go.
你可以吗？
You got her?
操
Fuck.
-快走 -等一下
-We have to go. -Just hang on.
你坐在后座好吗？快点儿
Let's load you up in the back, all right? Come on.
诺拉
Nora.
你会没事儿的
You're gonna be okay.
铃声
I hear bells...
-什么 -好了 走 走 走
-What? - All right. Go, go, go.
她说什么？
What did she say?
好了 好了 快走
All right, all right. Let's go.
开始了
It's happening.
莱莉 你到底走不走 你准备赶在后面跑回去吗？
Riley, you coming with us or following behind?
快走 我可不想待在这儿
Yeah. Let's get the fuck out of here.
快点 走 走 走
Hurry, go, go, go.
诺拉 清醒一点 别睡啊
Nora. Hey, stay with me, babe.
别睡 坚持住啊 好吗？
Come on, keep your eyes open for me, okay?
该死
Oh, shit.
这他妈是什么？
What is that? Fuck.
快点 快点 快点
Come on, come on, come on.
崔弗
Trevor...
-操 -这又怎么了？
-Fuck. -What is it doing?
这个盒子在变 我也不知道怎么了
It's changing. I don't know.
它到底要怎样？
What the hell is it doing?
-我也不知道 -要变成啥？
-I don't know. -Changing into what?
刚刚该转弯的 走过了
That's the turn. We missed it.
主路应该在左变
No. The main road's left.
不 应该在前面转弯
No, it's not. It was just here.
我们刚才就在这儿 好吧？
Yeah, so were we, all right?
操
Fuck!
-走 快开啊 -我正开着呢
-Go, go, go. -Yeah, I'm going.
咱们迷路了？
Are we lost?
我们走错路了 往回开啊
We're going down the wrong road. Go back.
-没走错 -不 走错方向了啊
-No, we're not. -Yes, we're going the wrong way!
科林？
Colin?
莱莉？
Riley?
糟了
Oh, shit.
上帝啊 求求你上帝
Oh, God, please, God.
我们的天父啊 您的名号如此神圣···
Our Father who art in Heaven, hallowed be thy name...
你在祈祷什么？
What is it you pray for?
救赎
Salvation.
那会是什么感觉？
And what would it feel like?
如音符般愉悦吗？
A joyful note?
没有改变
Without change,
没有休止？
without end?
天堂？
Heaven?
天堂里可没有音乐
There's no music in that.
求求你···
Please...
但是这···
But this...
人的身体能被迫体会相当多的感觉
There is so much more the body can be made to feel.
在我们结束之前
And you'll feel it all.
你会全部感受一遍
Before we're through.
诺拉
Nora!
我操什么鬼？
What the fuck?
天啊
Holy shit!
诺拉
Nora!
你说对了 我们当初该扔了这玩意儿
You were right. We should have thrown it away.
我不该···
I shouldn't...
你们不应该在这里 也不应该来这里
You shouldn't be here right now. You guys shouldn't be here.
我们自己决定过来
We came on our own.
不 你们是为了我 因为这是我的错
No, you came because of me, because it's my fault.
没时间说谁对谁错了
We don't have time for this.
没时间说这些了
抱歉 是真得快点了
I'm sorry, but we don't.
好吗？我们得叫警察来
Okay? We need to call the cops.
得让警察搜查这里
We need to let them search.
也行他们能找到她
Okay. Maybe they'll find her.
-那谁知道呢？ -他们找不到她的
-Who knows? -They're not gonna find her.
那就找不到 不过我可不想在这里
Then they won't, but I have no interest
继续待下去了 行吧？
in hanging around here any longer, okay?
咱们得回到房子里去
We have to get back to the house.
-操他妈的房子 -什么？
-Fuck that house. -What?
莱莉的车就在那边 好吗？
Listen, that's where Riley's car is. Okay?
那房子里没啥好事 崔弗
There is nothing good in that house, Trevor.
这我明白
Okay, I understand that.
但是我们得做决定了
But we have to make decisions here.
我们到了那里 再决定下一步干什么
Once we get there, then we can talk about what we wanna do next.
或者争论是谁的错或者其他的···
Or who's fault it is or whatever the fuck we want to...
别你妈在这儿高高在上的跟我说话
Do not fucking talk down to me.
-我没有··· -别觉得自己很牛逼···
-I'm not... -Do not talk down to me...
等一下
Wait.
还不到时候
Not yet.
接受这痛苦
Accept the pain
你自己铸就的痛苦
you have wrought.
无上的欢愉等着你
Greater delights await.
我们希望你继续下去
We wish to see you proceed.
-我不想要这一切发生 -但一切已经发生
-I didn't ask for this. -But you did.
这是什么东西？
What are you?
我们探索更为宽广的境界
Explorers in the further regions of experience.
探索感知的边缘
Of sensation's rim.
我们的礼物是无限的
Our gifts are boundless.
-可我不想要 -不 你想要
-I don't want them. -Yes, you do.
我们的神在等待
Our God awaits.
你知道神可赠予你什么
You know what it can offer.
复活？
Resurrection?
你哥哥的结局很精致
Your brother's ending was exquisite.
什么？
What?
如果再见他一面会给你带来宽慰吗？
Would it bring you comfort to see him again?
莱莉
Riley!
你在哪儿？
Where are you?
再献祭两个便将他归还于你
Two more and he is yours.
喂养它吧
Feed it.
用他们的痛苦
Their pain.
用他们的鲜血
Their blood.
解锁下一个形态
Unlock the next configuration.
知道最终的形态
And then the last.
不
No.
我做错的事够多了
I've done enough.
“足够”
Enough
只不过是你们的错误想法
is a myth.
我们不接受拒绝
We will not be denied.
你的鲜血现在掌握再我们手中
Your blood is in our hands now.
我们随时可以过来收集你
Ours to claim at any time.
但是我吧盒子留在你这里
But the box I leave in yours.
你或其他人 选择吧
If not you, another. Choose.
还需要两个人
Two more.
莱莉
Riley!
你在哪儿？
Where are you?
莱莉
Riley!
嘿 嘿
Hey, hey.
操
Fuck.
早了 宝贝
Oh, shit, babe.
你干了啥？
What did you do?
不是我干的
It wasn't me.
-不是我 -好了 没事 没事
-It wasn't me. -All right, come on, come on.
没关系 我们走吧
It's okay. Let's just go.
我们继续走
Let's just keep walking.
好
Okay.
莱莉 嘿
Riley. Hey.
你没事吧？
Are you good?
你还好吗？
Are you okay?
嘿 看着我
Hey, look at me.
-我不会做的 -什么？
-I'm not gonna do it. -What?
我不会把你们献祭出去
I'm not gonna offer you up.
那他妈是什么东西？
What the fuck is that?
我的妈呀
What the fuck...
你他妈干什么呢？赶紧跑啊
The fuck are you doing? Let's go! Come on!
快翻过去 莱莉 快
Come on, Riley. Come on.
-科林 科林 快起来 -科林
-Colin. Colin, get up. -Colin!
科林 起来 你在干什么？
Colin, get up! What are you doing?
-科林 快点哥们 -站起来
-Colin, come on, man. -Stand up!
站起来
Stand up!
不 不
No, no.
不 不 不
No, no, no.
加油 加油推啊
Come on, come on. Push!
不
No!
加油
Come on!
莱莉
Riley!
莱莉 莱莉 莱莉
Riley, Riley. Riley!
莱莉
Riley!
莱莉 救我
Riley, come on!
操
Fuck.
Fuck!
嘿 大家 他们又来了
Hey, guys. They're coming again.
咱们怎么办？莱莉
What do we do? Riley!
我们该怎么办？
What are we gonna do?
快跑
Let's go.
快点
Come on, hurry.
快
Come on.
赶紧起来
Get the fuck up.
快跑
Move! Hurry!
-我的天啊 -他要失血过多了
-Oh, my God. -He's bleeding a lot.
我感觉他要进入休克状态了
I think he's going to start going into shock.
等下 莱莉 你他妈去哪儿啊？
Wait, Riley. Where the fuck are you going?
我们做了什么 我们都他妈干了什么？
What have we done? What the hell have we done now?
天哪
Holy shit.
你刚才到底干什么了？
What the fuck did you just do?
我按了一下开关
I hit the switch.
我们必须尽快止血或者尽可能让血流得慢一点
We have to stop the bleeding or at least slow it down a little bit.
-操 行了 把你的腰带给我 -什么？
-Fuck, okay. Give me your belt. -What?
把你的腰带给我！
Give me your fucking belt!
天哪
Jesus.
好了
Okay.
一 二 三！
One, two, three!
好了
Okay.
让他在这里躺下来
Lay him down right here.
-好了 抬着他的腿 -挺住
-Okay, get his legs. -Come on.
不 不 不
No, no, no.
操 我们得找东西给他包扎手臂
Fuck, we need to find something for his arm.
他流了太多血
Damn, that's a lot of blood.
这些药效太猛了
These are strong.
你先拿着吧 他之后可能会用到
You should hold onto these in case he needs them later.
我来···
Let me, um...
我也给你找点包扎的东西吧
Let me find something for your hand, too.
-好 -我找找
-Okay. -Yeah.
谢谢
Thank you.
他们还在那里吗？
Are they still there?
在 但他们不动了
Yeah. Yeah, they're not moving.
我觉得是金属框架的作用
It's the metal framework, I think.
这些金属框架把整座房子围了起来
That runs along the whole house.
把他们挡在了外面
It keeps them out.
这能挡多久？
It keeps them out for how long?
崔弗撑不了多久的
Trevor's not gonna last.
我们怎么办？
What are we gonna do?
你走吧
You're gonna go.
-你得带着崔弗一起走 -走哪儿去？你想什么呢？
-You have to take Trevor and go. -Go where? What are you... What?
他们有我的血 你知道的吧？
They have my blood. You realize that, right?
-他们要找的是我 -别说了
-It's me that they're after. -Stop.
除非我牺牲你们中的一个人 但是我不会
Unless I give them one of you, and I won't.
-我不要再失去任何一个人了 -我也不要
-I'm not losing anyone else. -Neither am I.
而且···
Besides...
我真的不想冒险跑出去
I don't really feel like taking my chances with those things.
你还有其他计划吗？
So, what else you got?
罗兰
Roland.
嘿 对不起 对不起
Hey, I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
听我说 事情出了点变故 我知道
Listen, things got a little out of control, okay? I know it.
本来不应该是这样的 但是你听我说
It's not exactly what was supposed to happen, but listen.
-听我说··· -别说话
-Listen... -Shh, shh!
你的职责很简单
All you had to do
把那个盒子喂足血
was feed the box
-并且拿回来 -我照你说的做了
-and bring it back! -I did, I did.
沃伊特先生 我照你说的做了
Mr. Voight, I did.
我···
Okay? I...
她已经被标记了 她已经被标记了
She was a mark. She was a mark.
我和她一起的 但是她带着盒子走了
I brought her along and she ran with it.
盒子本来是该收下她的 好吗？但是我···
I mean, it was supposed to take her, okay? But I...
你是个胆小鬼 你本该自己打开的
You're a coward. You should have opened it yourself.
你应该确保万无一失
You should have made sure.
这没关系 问题不大
Okay, it doesn't matter. It doesn't matter.
好吧？她抢先了我几步 但这又如何
All right? She got a little ahead of me. So what?
这又怎样？
So what?
她自己把血给了盒子 还把它带到了这里
She fed it on her own, and she brought it here.
对不对？
Right?
事情不总是一帆风顺 对吧？这我承认
Things took a turn, all right? I admit that.
但是一切都在掌控中
But I'm handling it.
一切都回归正轨了 盒子就差最后一个形态了
We're on track, we're one configuration away.
你就要成功了
You're almost there.
赶快搞定
Finish it.
就快结束了 耐心点
It's finishing itself. Just be patient.
啊
Argh!
耐心？
Patience?
每一秒对我都是煎熬！
Every second is a lifetime!
帮我把我身上的东西取掉
Get it out of me.
操
Fuck.
既然这东西对那个大块头有用对他们其他人应该也有用
It worked on the big one. We have to assume it'll work on another.
所以你要放一个进来？
Okay, so you want to let one in?
是的 我知道 但是就放一个
Yes, I know. Just one, though.
我们引诱一个进来 把后面的都关在外面
We let one in, lure it in, shut the thing behind it,
然后我就上去捅它
and then I stab it.
你醒了
You're awake.
发生什么事了？
What's going on?
莱莉有个计划
Riley has a plan.
你能动了吗？
You good to move?
我猜我没办法叫你改变主意了？
I don't guess I can get you to reconsider?
你没法叫我做任何事
No, you can't get me to do anything.
就算我也想你能劝我不去
Even when I want you to.
开门
Do it.
我不确定要不要继续
I don't know about this.
-我要出去了 -莱···
-I'm going out there. -Ri...
把我带走吧
Take me!
像带走他们一样带走我
Take me like you took them!
像带走我哥哥一样
Like you took my brother.
带走他们？
Take them?
我们给了他们自由
We set them free.
释放自己吧
Release yourself.
是时候了 回去吧
Now. Come on.
别让他们碰到···
Don't let them touch...
小心
Be careful.
快跑
Run!
崔弗 快关门
Trevor, the switch!
莱莉 莱莉
Riley! Riley!
科林
Colin!
你还好吗？
You good?
怎么了？
What's happening?
-我没事 -那就好
-I'm okay. -Okay.
它在干什么？
What's it doing?
-我感觉它被卡住了 -赶快把那鬼东西给杀了！
-I think it's stuck! -Just kill the fucking thing!
杀不了 盒子不在我手上
I can't. I don't have the box.
我绊倒的时候弄掉了
I dropped it when I fell.
好吧 让我进来
Okay, let me in.
让我进来！
Let me in!
-在哪里？ -在你右手边的地板上
-Where is it? -It's on the floor to your left.
我就是在那里摔倒的
That's where I fell.
-我撞上了那个东西 -好的 好的
-I ran into that thing there. -Okay. Okay.
赶快
Please hurry.
我没看到
I don't see it.
就在那边的地上
It's just right there on the ground.
-我什么都没看到 莱莉 -我不知道还能在哪里
-I'm not seeing anything, Riley. -I don't know where else it'll be.
我就把它丢在了那里
I dropped it right there.
-我找不到 -什么情况？怎么会找不到呢？
-I can't find it. -What do you mean, you can't find it?
盒子不在地上 其他地方也没有
It's not on the floor. I'm not seeing it anywhere.
-糟了 科林
-Shit. -Colin!
不
No!
不 不 不
No, no, no!
科林
Colin!
你不用杀人的！
You didn't have to do that!
刀片的划伤就能害死他们！
The blade would've taken them!
没关系了
It doesn't matter.
地狱苦行僧要来了
The cenobites will come
正如我期待的一样
just like I want them to.
我的天哪
Oh, my God.
他是罗兰·沃伊特
That's Roland Voight.
崔弗 是他！
Trevor, that's him!
是我本人
In the flesh
真是在下
such as it is.
但他已经知道了 对不对
But then he already knew that, didn't you,
崔弗？
Trevor?
你早就知道？
You knew?
原来你早就知道！
You knew!
你把那东西交到我手上 你早就知道
You put that thing in my hands and you knew.
你怎么能这么做？为什么要这么做？
How could you do that? Why would you do that?
对不起
Sorry.
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
你怎么能这样？
How could you do that?
他只是拿钱办事罢了
He was just doing what I paid him to.
并且后面还会帮我办事
And he will continue to do so
因为这是他可怜的一生中最好的活了
because this is the best deal of his miserable life.
那是什么？
What is that?
这他妈的是怎么回事？
What the fuck is happening?
这不很明显吗？
Isn't it obvious?
我接受了奖赏
I claimed my reward.
我已经经历了
I had experienced
常人所能够经历的一切
everything afforded to man,
可是
and still,
我还想得到更多
I wanted more.
我选择了“阈值之盒”
I chose Liminal.
我选择了感觉
I chose sensation.
可地狱苦行僧
But the cenobites,
他们的喜好和我想象的不一样
their tastes were not what I imagined.
他们让我心神不定
They preyed on my nerves.
胡乱拉扯我的神经 以至于···
Pulling them in random cycles, stopping just enough...
···因此我时刻感受着痛苦
...so I could never grow numb.
我不知道他们许诺给你什么
I don't know what they promised you.
知识？爱？
Knowledge? Love?
我追求快乐
I sought pleasure.
可他们给我的
But all they have to give
只有痛苦
is pain.
这是个骗局
It's a trick.
全部都是
All of it.
把它打开
Open it.
不要
Don't.
崔弗 你在做什么？
Trevor, what are you doing, man?
让他们进来
Letting them in.
不 不要！
No, don't!
科林
Colin.
-科林 快走 -我做不到
-Colin, go. -I can't.
快起来 你得离开这里
Get up. You have to go.
房间开始旋转了
The room is spinning.
科林 快起来！我在这边没办法帮忙
Colin, get up! I can't help you from here.
你得站起来赶快离开
You have to get up and go.
听我说
Listen to me.
-好的 -他们要来了 你得赶紧走！
-Okay. -They're gonna come. You have to go!
门开了
The gate's open.
快点！
Hurry!
快走！
Go!
-看住他 -科林 科林 科林
-Watch him. -Colin, Colin, Colin.
-都结束了老兄 都结束了 -快走 快起来
-It's over, man. It's over. -Go, get up.
我们得让他待在这里
We need him close by.
很好 拿去吧
Yes. Take it.
我把他们的血
I give you their blood,
他们的痛苦都给你
their suffering.
快来拿吧 混蛋
Come get it, you bastard.
我还在这里
I'm still here
我要求见面！
and I demand an audience!
科林！
Colin!
科林···
Colin...
结束了
It's over.
快回房间 他们要来了
Get back to the room because they're coming.
我们已经来了
We're already here.
不
No.
你够不到我
Your chains can't reach me here.
告诉你的神 我捉到了它的门族
Tell your God I've got its disciples.
它的传教者
Its priest.
你以为我做了什么？建一个堡垒吗？
What did you think? I built a fortress?
我建了一个笼子！
I built a cage!
在你们的神让我恢复容貌之前 我是不会放你们走的
And I'm not letting any of you go until it makes me right again.
你拒绝了我们的礼物
You reject our gift.
去你妈的礼物！
Fuck your gift!
去你妈的！
Fuck you!
把这个东西从我身体里拿出去
Now take it out of me.
真不简单
Remarkable.
这一切···
All this...
都是为我们准备的
All for us.
不是为你们准备的
No, not for you.
是为了我自己
For me.
我想要的东西就一定要得到
I get what I want.
那就让我们进来
Then let us in
结束你的痛苦
to address your displeasure.
你在做什么？
What are you doing?
不是很明显吗？
Isn't it obvious?
等等
Wait.
把它收回去吧
Just take it back.
把它收回去吧 我不想要了
Just take it back. I don't want it anymore.
停下
Stop!
把它取出来吧
Just take it out.
我不想要了
I don't want it anymore.
让我死吧 求求你了
Just let me die. I'm begging you.
求你···
Just...
让我死吧
Just let me die.
没有后悔的余地
There is no retreat.
一旦界限被穿过
Once a threshold has been crossed,
你能做的只有找到更大的界限
all you can do is search for greater thresholds.
不是他 我没有选择他
Not him. I never chose him.
但是他被选中了
And yet he is chosen.
他有标记
Marked.
礼物不能收回
Gifts cannot be ungiven.
只能做交易
Only exchanges can be made.
有人告诉我那个盒子在我手里
I was told that the box is in my hands.
如果不是我 就是另一个
If not me, another.
对吗？
Right?
-不是他 -莱莉 你在做什么？
-Not him. -Riley, what are you doing?
或许你更喜欢···
Perhaps you'd prefer...
另一个
Another.
怎么样都比现在好
Anything is better than this.
也许我们之前
Perhaps we were wrong
看错你了
about you.
你从未追求过感觉
You've never sought sensation.
你的整个人生
Your whole life,
每一次征服
every conquest,
你所有的快乐
all your pleasures
都建立在“力量”之上
lie in power.
力量
Power.
鉴于你所做的努力
For your efforts,
我们为你提供利维坦形态
we offer the Leviathan configuration.
莱莉 莱莉 等一下 等一下
Riley, Riley. Hold on. Hold on.
我试图阻止你的 还记得吗？
I tried to stop you, remember?
对吗？
Yeah?
把那个鬼东西放下
Just put the fucking thing down.
好吗？
Okay?
把它给我！
Give it to me!
我们的力量来自支配
Our power lies in dominance,
我们可以随意操控痛苦
in the sovereignty of anguish.
现在
And now,
由你来驾驭力量
it will be yours to wield.
不···
No...
你会见识到我们最好的礼物
You will know our finest gift.
-不！ -没错
-No! -Oh, yes.
我们要向你展示非常壮观的景象
We have such sights to show you.
去吧
Go.
不
No.
我没事的
I'll be fine. Okay?
去结束这一切吧
Just finish it.
哀痛之盒 学识之盒
Lament, Lore,
赞誉之盒
Laudarant,
阈值之盒 拉撒路之盒 利维坦之盒
Liminal, Lazarus, Leviathan.
你想从我们这里得到什么？
What would you ask of us?
莱莉···
Riley...
莱莉 看着我
Riley, look at me.
拉着我的手
Take my hand.
带我回家
Take me home.
不
No.
我见过你们的奖赏···
I've seen your rewards...
我知道我哥哥已经死了
I know my brother's gone.
我不想从你们那里得到任何东西
I don't want anything from you.
-我什么也不要 -那你选择了···
-Nothing. -Then you have chosen...
一生的悔恨
A life of regret.
你后悔你所做的一切 你伤害并失去的
Knowing everything you've done, everyone you've hurt
每一个人
and lost.
你的苦难才刚刚开始
Your suffering has barely begun.
你选择活下去 承受这份痛苦
You chose to live, to carry that weight.
你的一生痛苦而短暂
Bitter and brief.
你选择了哀痛之盒
You have chosen the Lament Configuration.
刚刚发生什么了？
What just happened in there?
我做出了选择
I made a choice.
你做了正确的选择
It was the right one.
对吗？
Right?
罗兰 时机已到
Roland, it's time.